smokoo.com 2016-11-02

# Privacy Policy - Smokoo.com

  * This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms of Use Agreement and the definitions contained therein shall have reference herein. The Terms of Use Agreement can be located on our Website (www.smokoo.com)
  * Smokoo collects information about you by requesting necessary information directly from you usually using a contact form. We use this information to ensure that we can provide you with the best possible and most customised service and products possible.
  * The information we collect is stored on secure servers that are not open to the public and are access controlled to ensure that your information remains secure. You hereby consent to Smokoo storing such information in any territory it deems appropriate, in Smokoo’s sole discretion. 
  * We may use the information we collect to better optimise our site or to get a statistical overview of our site visitors. All personal information that we collect will be treated as strictly confidential and will not be shared with any other third party service without your express permission.
  * Save as provided for the Terms of Use, Smokoo will only disclose personal information when we are required to do so by law, we believe that fraudulent action is taking place or it is in the best interest of protecting the company or our clients.
  * We may use the information that you have provided us to send you emails about promotional offers we believe may be of interested to you. However, should you wish to not receive promotional or marketing communications from us, you can send an email to info@smokoo.com and your information will be removed from our distribution lists.
  * Furthermore, if you would like to have your personal information removed from our servers in its entirety, or would like to change the particulars of your personal information, please send an email to info@smokoo.com.
  * Our Website makes use of cookies. Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer so that we can help make your visit to our site more convenient by keeping a record of your visits.
  * Additionally, we also make use of third party site advertising and utilise cookies to target adverts to people who have visited our site before. When you browse the Website, we send advertising cookies to your computer to better understand your interests. AdRoll, a third party company, then uses this information to provide you with targeted advertising based on your browsing habits and, in particular, your previous interactions with our website.
  * The information we collect using cookies does not include any personal information. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name or contact details.
  * By using the Site, you agree to accept cookies.
  * However, if you do not want to accept cookies, you can change the privacy settings on your computer’s browser. Please note that this may cause certain features on the Site to not work as effectively. Furthermore, you may also opt out of targeting for third party site advertising by visiting Google advertising opt-out page.
  * Our Site may contain links to third party sites which are governed by their own privacy policies. The onus of responsibility remains with you to check these privacy policies before using these sites.
  * Should you wish to correct, update or delete any personal information, you may do so by contacting us at info@smokoo.com.
  * This privacy policy may be updated at any time without any prior notice.
